本字幕由好字幕网www.haosub.com中文站搜集整理
转载请保留字幕者信息若压制组修改字幕组信息必须举报，请珍惜他人劳动果实谢谢配合
我是Max
My name is Max.
我活在战火与鲜血的世界里
My world is fire and blood.
曾经，我是一名警察
Once, I was a cop.
一名寻求正义的公路战士
A road warrior searching for a righteous cause.
当世界沦陷...
As the world fell...
我们每个人都从某种意义上损坏了
each of us in our own way was broken.
很难说谁比谁更疯狂
It was hard to know who was more crazy.
我...
Me...
或是其他任何人
Or everyone else.
在吗？
Hello?
你在哪？
Where are you?
Max你在哪？
Where are you Max?
他们又来了
Here they come again.
钻进我脑子里的黑暗物质
Worming their way into the black matter of my brain.
救救我们！你答应过会救我们的！
Help us Max!  You promised to help us!
我告诉自己...
I tell myself...
他们伤不了我
they cannot touch me.
他们早死了
They are long dead.
我可是那个...
I am the one...
从活人和死人那里都要逃掉的人
who runs from both the living AND the dead.
被拾荒者追捕...
Hunted by scavengers...
被我未曾保护的人缠绕
Haunted by those I could not protect.
我能存在于这个不毛之地
So I exist in this wasteland...
就是因为我仅存的本能：
A man, reduced to a single instinct:
生存
Survive.
血型 O型阴性 高辛烷值 万能供血者
Blood group O negative, high octane.
Universal donor.
Max?
是你吗？
Is that you?
帮帮我们！
Help us!
Max 你在哪？！
Max Where are you?!
别再跑了 Max！
Stop running Max！
别跑了！
Stop running!
他害死了我们！
He made us die!
我们是战争之子！
We are War Boys!
战争之子！
War Boys!
神风敢死队！
Kamikrazee War Boys!
战争之子！
War Boys!
衔接！
Hooked On!
今天我们要去汽油镇！
Today we're headed to Gas Town!
汽油镇！
Gas Town!
今天我们要为大家带来纯净的水
Today we haulin' Aqua Cola.
纯净的水！
Aqua Cola!
今天我们要为大家带来水果和蔬菜！ 水果蔬菜！
Today we carry fruits and vegetables!
Fruits and vegetables!
总之今天我们要为大家带来好东西！
And today we carry mother's milk!
好东西！
Mother's Milk!
乔！乔！乔！不死老乔！
Joe! Joe! Joe! immortan Joe!
热烈欢迎 不死老乔！！！
Give it up, for the immortan Joe!!!
又一次，我们派我的武装车...
Once again, we send off my
War Rig to bring back...
从汽油镇带回了汽油...
guzzoline from Gas Town...
还有从子弹农场带来的子弹！
and bullets from the Bullet Farm!
我再一次，向我们的指挥官Furiosa...
Once again, I salute
to my Imperator...
致敬!
Furiosa!
我还要向
And I salute...
我英勇的战争之子们致敬...
my half-life War Boys...
他们将在去英灵殿的路上...
who will ride with me, eternal...
一直与我相伴
on the highways of Valhalla.
V8! V8! V8! V8!
我是你们的救世主
I AM YOUR REDEEMER!
追随着我...
It is by my hand...
你们就会在这世间的尘土中...
you will rise from the ashes...
崛起！
of this world!
要来了 准备好
It's coming. Get ready.
是的 没错 水要来了
Yes. Yes. The water comes.
我的朋友们...
Do not, my friends...
不要对水产生依赖
become addicted to water.
它会支配你...
It will take hold of you...
而你，会因为没有水而感到沮丧
and you will resent, it's absence.
滚开！
Get out!
都给我滚开！
Get rid of them all!
滚开！
Get out!
都给我滚开！
Get rid of them all!
滚！
Get out!
准备去汽油镇 带上一个车队
Signal Gas Town.
Convoy's on it's way.
这个战争之子快不行了
I got a War Boy
running on empty.
给那个满血的接上
Hook-up that full-life.
嘿，小心! !他是万能供血者
Hey, careful!! He's a universal donor.
老大，我们不去汽油镇了吗？
Boss, we're not going to Gas Town?
是去子弹农场吗？
Bullet Farm?
我们要向东走！
We're heading east!
我会把命令传达给大家的
I'll pass it down the line.
新命令！
New orders!
全速前进！全速前进！
Thunder up! Thunder up!
这不是供给之旅
This is not a supply run!!
Go! Go!
什么鬼？发生什么了？
What is this? What's going on??
我们要向东走
We're heading east.
为啥？
Why?
我不知道，这是命令
I don't know, that's the orders.
老爸！！
Hey Pa!!
你知道吗？
You know about this?
他们并没有去汽油镇
You're produce ain't going to Gas Town.
她离开了车道
She's gone off road...
开向了敌人的地盘
into hostile territory.
为什么她要这么做？
Why would she do that Dad?
让我看看！让我看看！
Lemme see! Lemme see!!
我想看！！
I wanna see!!
去看看是什么烦着老爸！！
Go see what's agitating DAD!!
Splendid?!
Angharad?!!
我们的孩子不会成为暴君
OUR BABIES WILL NOT BE WARLORDS.
是谁毁了世界？
WHO KILLED THE WORLD?
她们去哪了？
Where are they?
她们不是你的财产！！
They are not your property!!
Miss Giddy!!
你不能占有人类
You cannot own a human being.
我们不是物品
WE ARE NOT THINGS.
早晚会有人造反的！
Sooner or later someone pushes back!
她带他们去哪了！！！
WHERE IS SHE TAKING THEM?!!!
不是她带她们走的 是她们求她的！
She didn't take them.They begged her to go!
她带他们去哪了？
Where is she taking them?
一个远离你的地方！
A long way from you!!!
发生什么了？
What's happened?
Slit!
怎么了？Slit！    叛国！
What's going on? Slit!!   Treason!
背叛了！指挥官背叛了！
Betrayal! An Imperator gone rogue.
指挥官？ 是谁？
Imperator? Who?
Furiosa！她把老乔的东西带走了
Furiosa! She took a lot of stuff
from Immortan Joe.
什么东西？
What stuff?
母种！他珍贵的母种！
Breeders! His prized Breeders!!
他还想让她们活着回来
He wants them back! Not a hand laid on 'em.
荣耀为名
By my deeds I honor him.
V8.
V8! V8! V8!
这是我的方向盘！！    我要开车！
That's my wheel!!    I'm driving!
你是我的投手
You're my lancer.
我刚刚给自己升了职！
I just promoted myself!!!
今天不行 今天是我的日子！
Not today. Today is my day!
你看看你 站都站不起来 还想打仗！
Look at you. If you can't stand up,
you can't do war!!
他说的没错，孩子
He's right, son.
我不会在这里软弱地死去！！
I'm not staying here dying a sloth!!
你已经是个死人了
You're already a corpse.
我只需要补一点点血
I just need a little top-up.
已经没有时间了！
There's no time!!!
我们可以带着我的血包
We take my Blood Bag.
我们把血包绑在车前
We'll take my Blood Bag
and string him to the lancer's perch.
这玩意戴着面具 他是个疯子！！
It's got a muzzle on it. It's a
raging feral!!
没错！我会用烈性疯狂的血液来填补自己
That's right!High-octane crazy blood filling me up.
如果我死了
If I'm gonna die...
我也要在狂暴之路上留名青史！
I'm gonna die historic on the Fury Road!
好！好！
Yeah! Yeah!!
Organic，把他的血包绑上去
Organic, hitch up his Blood Bag.
好的
Right-o.
他们还能从我这抢走什么？
What else can they take from me?
不但了抽我的血
They have my blood.
还抢走我的车！
Now it's my car!
不朽！
Immortan!
不死老乔！
Immortan Joe!
他看了我一眼！
He looked at me!
He looked right at me!
他看的是你的血包！
He was staring at your Blood Bag!
他回了头！直视着我的眼睛！
He turned his head! He looked
me straight in the eye!!
他只是看着地平线！
He was scanning the horizon!
不
No.
我期待着！
I am awaited!
我期待着进入英灵殿！
I am awaited in Valhalla!!!!
FUCK!!!!!
不朽
Immortan!
看！ 快看！
Look! Hey look!!
看！
Look!!
老大！
Boss!
我看到从大本营里出来的车辆 他们发射了信号弹
We got vehicles from the Citadel. They're firing flares.
看起来他们要给汽油镇和子弹农场增员
They want reinforcements from Gas Town and the Bullet Farm.
怎么回事？
What is this??
支援？诱饵？
Backup? Decoy??
这是个迂回
It's a detour.
那辆武装车想对我们做什么？
What's this War Rig doing on our patch!?
作死 但是随时欢迎
Foolish...but welcome
秃鹫帮派！
Buzzards!!!
秃鹫帮派在右边！注意！注意！
Buzzards right!! Eyes on! Eyes on!!
我们是不是该掉头和后援会和？
Should we turn around and
run 'em into our backup?
不需要！我们可以做到
No! We're good.
我们会击败他们！
We fang it!!
全速前进！我们走！
Thunder up! Here we go!!
准备射击！
Prepare the shooter!
Morsov!
战争！
War!
准备！
Ready!
她是我们的 Slit！她是我们的！
She's ours Slit! She's ours!!
我们首先要干掉她后面的秃鹫帮派！
First, we get the buzzards off her back!
准备投掷！
Ready to throw!
那可是我的脑袋！
That's my head!!!
振作起来！你能做到的！
Get up! You can do it!
Morsov!
Morsov！   不！
Morsov!    No!
见证我吧！
WITNESS ME!!!
我来见证！    我来见证！
Witness!     Witness!!!
见证！ 见证！
Witness!!! I Witness!
平庸的Morsov
Mediocre Morsov!!
Mediocre!!!!
靠过去！
Get me in!
他们来啦！
They are coming!
我们在下面没法呼吸了！
We can't breathe down there!!
别让他们发现你！
Stay outta sight!!
快！
NOW!!!
回来！
Back!
发生什么了？！
What happened?!
液压装置！液压装置！！
Hydraulics! Hydraulics!!
现在该把战利品带回家了
Now we bring home the booty.
她以为她能甩掉我们的父亲！
She thinks she can lose us Dad!
她以为我们很蠢！
She thinks we're stupid.
她以为在那里能甩掉我们！
She thinks she can lose us
in there!
冲锋！
Fang it!
冲啊！！
FANG IT!!!
为什么你不停下来？
Why can't you stop?
嘿！靠边去！靠边去！
You! Outta the way! Out of the way!!!
你都干了什么？！
What have you done?!
你都干了些什么？！
我们需要平衡 把血包挪到后面去
We need a counterweight.
Get the Blood Bag toward the back.
烧死他们！烧死他们！
Burn them! Burn them!
嘿！
Hey there!
和脖子说再见吧！
Say bye bye to the neck!
我们要进去了 Slit！
We're going in Slit!
快点！我们马上就能追上她了！
Come on! We almost got it!
来吧！稳住！
Come on! Hold!
哦多棒的一天！ 多么美好的一天！！
Oh what a day! WHAT A LOVELY DAY!!
我就是那个...
I'm the man...
霸占了太阳...
who grabbed the sun...
驶向英灵殿的人！！！
riding to Valhalla!!!!
见证我吧 血包！
Witness me Blood Bag!!
见证我！！
Witness!!!
生存 死亡 重生！
I live, I die, I live again!!
我们是不会回去的
We're not going back.
水
Water.
你
You.
Angharad，那只不过是风...
Angharad, is that just the wind...
还是热闹的影像？
or a furious fixation?
我拿到了！
I got it!
太棒了血包！ 她的死活掌控在我们手中了
Glory me Blood Bag! We snagged her alive.
他会把她撕碎   撕碎！
He's gonna shred her. Shred Her!!
拿钳子
Bolt cutters.
链条
Chain.
嘿 嘿 嘿！
Hey, hey, HEY!!
哦 看看他们
Ohh look at them.
多么闪耀！多么辉煌
So shiny! So chrome.
他会非常感激我们的！
He's gonna be so grateful!
我们可以索求任何东西
We could ask for anything.
我想开这辆武装车
I want to drive the War Rig.
你想要什么？
What will you ask for?
我要我的夹克！
That's MY Jacket!!
当然
Sure.
我是说 你可以索要比这更好的东西
I mean, you could ask for
more than a jacket.
我们要去绿洲
We're going to the Green Place.
我们要去绿洲 安置众多母亲的绿洲
We're going to the Green Place
of Many Mothers.
你感觉如何？
How does it feel?
很疼！
It hurts!
在外的一切都会很痛
Out here everything hurts.
你想要渡过难关？
You wanna get through this?
那就照我说的做
Do as I say.
拿起你们能拿的东西 快跑
Now pick up what you can and run.
肮脏！
Filth!
煞死开关
Kill switches.
我自己设计的一套熄火装置
I set the sequence myself.
这辆车没了我哪都去不了
This Rig goes nowhere without me.
你可以进来
You can get in.
但不能丢下他们
Not without them.
那我们就等着吧
So we wait.
你觉得那个混蛋会对你心存感激？
You're relying on the gratitude
of a very bad man.
你已经伤了他的一个妻子 你觉得他还会感激你吗？
You've already damaged one of his wives.
How grateful do you think he's gonna be?
你现在坐在一台2000马力的战争机器里
You're sitting on 2000 horsepower
of Nitro-boosted war machine.
我认为你还有五分钟可以抢先
I think you've got a five minute headstart.
你还想不想吧面具拿下来？！
You want that thing off your face?!
我们走！
Let's go!
你射谁不好，那个可是老乔的最爱
Of all the legs you had to shoot,
that one was attached to his favorite.
你没必要听命于他
You don't have to do it
just because he tells you.
她有选择吗？
What choice does she have?
他不会伤害我们 他需要我们
He's not gonna hurt us. He needs us.
为什么？  这是笔交易
Why?    To bargain.
他不会伤害我们 这是肯定的
He won't hurt us.That's alright.
你觉得他会去绿洲吗？
Do you think he's coming
to the Green Place?
不会！他是个精神错乱的疯子 还喜欢吃人！
Never!He's a crazy lunatic who
likes to eat schlanger!
不在这边
Ahh stay outta there.
在你背后
Behind you.
汽油镇的人
Gas Town Boys.
别伤了好东西
Don't damage the goods.
你看到了什么？
What do you see?
大卡车...
Big rigs...
Polecats...
Flamers...
还有食人者他自己
and there's the People Eater himself!
该考虑一下战斗成本了
Coming to count the cost.
我们后面被拖住了！
We dragging something out back!
我觉得是后面的油罐
I think it's the fuel pod.
不 不！
No. NO!
我去
I'll go.
婊子！你背叛了他！
Bitch! You traitored him!
不！没必要杀他！
No unnecessary killing!!
这家伙想要我死！
This War Boy wants me dead!!
我们说好了的！
We agreed!!
他是敢死队的！
He's kamikrazee!!
他不过是个快死的孩子！
He just a kid at the end of his half-life!!
不！我活过 我死了 但我又重生了！
No! I live,
I die, I live again!!
控制住他！把他捆起来！
Hold him! I Tie him up!
把他扔出去！
Throw him out!
扔出去！
Throw him!
你们有伴了
You got more friends.
子弹农夫
Bullet Farmer.
他们从子弹农场来的
They're coming from the Bullet Farm.
是吗？
Yeah?
一切都结束了 你打不过他们！
It's over. You can't defy him!
你看着我们就行了！
Just watch us mate!
他就是那个占领太阳的人
He is the one who grabbed the sun.
他那么狡猾地耍了你！
Look how slick he's fooled you War Boy!
他是个将死之人
He's a lying old man.
在他的领导下我们都会崛起的！
By his hand we'll all be lifted up!
这就是为什么我们身上会有他的纹身！
That's why we have his logo seared on our backs!
“种畜！”
"Breeding stock!"
“战争炮灰！”
"Battle fodder!"
不 荣耀在等待着我！
No, I am awaited!!
你只是个将死之人的炮灰
You're an old man's battle fodder.
要做的就是除掉一切生灵！
Killing everyone and everything!!
我们没有责任
We are not to blame.
那是谁毁掉了世界？！
Then who killed the world?!!
我在前面有个交易
I made a deal up ahead.
Safe passage.
不知道交易能不能成功
I don't know if it's still any good.
大家都回到通道里
Get back in the hold.
别关门
Keep the hatch open.
我要你待在这里
I need you here.
你可能要驾驶这辆卡车
You may have to drive the rig.
你
You.
你留下
You stay.
你留在这
You stay there.
不论你做什么，都不要探头
Whatever you do, you can't be seen.
我答应过我一个人去...
I'm supposed to be alone.
完成这笔交易
That was the deal.
下来
Down here.
嘿
Hey.
你叫什么？
What's your name?
我要怎么称呼你？
What do I call you?
这重要吗？
Does it matter?
好吧
Fine.
待会我大喊“智障”
When I yell "Fool"...
你就马上开车走
you drive outta here
as fast as you can.
这是机关口令：
This is the sequence:
1  1  2
One. One. Two.
One.
红  黑  启动
Red. Black. Go.
懂了吗？
You have it?
全都在这了！
It's all here!
照你的要求 3000加仑的汽油全在这了！
3000 gallons of guzzoline, just like you asked!
我去把油管的链条剪开
I'm gonna unhitch the pod.
你们等下就制造山崩
You drop the rocks.
你说：
You said:
“可能会有几辆车追你”
"A few vehicles in pursuit.Maybe."
我们数了一共有三个车队！
We count three war parties!!!
是啊我真是不走运
Yeah well I got unlucky.
让我们开始吧！
Let's do this!
智障！！！
FOOL!!!!!
那是我们的燃料！
That's our fuel!!!
用粗齿锯开路！
Open the way for Ripsaw!
一旦我们清理了岩石...
Once I'm over...
就让大家通过
clear the rocks and lead everyone through.
不朽！
Immortan!
不死老乔！
Immortan Joe!
这有个家伙！他说他曾在武装卡车上面
I got a War Boy! Say's he was on the War Rig.
你！上车！
You! Climb aboard!
嘿！嘿！
Hey! HEY!
我拿到了他的鞋子！
I got his boot!
我拿到了那个血包的鞋子！
I got the Blood Bag's boot!!
带上我！
Take me!
我有他的鞋子！
I've got his boot!!!
这一切都是为了家庭争吵
All of this for a family squabble.
还有健康的孩子
Healthy babies.
给我装弹
Reload the clip.
我不能
I can't.
拿枪来！
Gun!!!
把枪给我！
Give me the gun!!
还没有装好！
It's not loaded yet!!
快！
Now!
我们是有约定的！
We had a deal!
Rictus!
那有娘儿们！
The wives!
不要用火焰喷射器！
No more flames!!
Splendid!
那是我的孩子！
That's my child!
我的财产！！
MY PROPERTY!!!!
不朽...
Immorta...
不朽 如果我上了车 我有方法能够进去
Immortan. If I get on the rig, there's a way inside.
你叫什么名字
What is your name?
我叫 Nux
It's Nux.
我会把锥刀刺进她身体 留最后一口气给您！
I'll pike her in the spine. Keep her breathing for ya!!
不
No.
直接干掉她
Put a bullet in her skull.
停下卡车 带回我的财产...
Stop the rig. Return my property...
我会亲自...
and I myself...
将你带到英灵殿！
will carry you to the Gates of Valhalla!
荣耀在等着我吗？
Am I awaited?
至高荣耀在等待着你
You will ride eternal...
闪耀无比 光彩夺目
shiny and chrome.
Rictus!
帮帮他
Help him aboard!
准备好了？
Ready?
去吧！
Here we go!
弱智！
Mediocre!
Schlanger!
小心！
Look out!
Angharad!
小心！！
Look out!!!
不！！   Angharad！
NO!!!    Angharad!!!
停下！ 调头开回去！
Stop!! Turn the rig around!!
回去找她！
Go back for her!!!
不
No.
跟他说掉头回去！
Tell him to turn the rig around!!
你看到了吗？
Did you see it?
我看到她被车轮碾过
She went under the wheels.
你亲眼看到了吗？！
Did you SEE it?!
我看到她被车轮碾过
She went under the wheels!
我们继续前进！
We keep moving!
不！！   我们继续前进！！
NO!!    WE KEEP MOVING!!
他根本不知道他在说什么！
He doesn't know what he's talking about!
无论发生什么，我们都要去绿洲！
Whatever happens, we're going to the Green Place!
什么鬼绿洲！我们连它在哪都不知道！
What stupid Green Place! We don't even know where it is!
你还好吗？  前进！
Are you alright? GO ON! GO ON!!!
Cheedo!
Cheedo 别做傻事
Cheedo, don't be stupid.
停下来！
Stop!
他会原谅我们 我知道他会的
He'll forgive us.I know he will.
已经没有回头路了！
There's no going back!
我们是他的珍宝！    Cheedo！
We were his treasures!   Cheedo!
他给了我们保护！他给了我们奢华的生活！
We were protected! He gave us a life of luxury!
这有什么错？         我们不是他的奴隶！
What's wrong with that?    We are not things!!
不！
No!
Cheedo 我们不是他的奴隶！
Cheedo, we are not things!
我们不是他的奴隶       我不想在听到这句话了！
We are not THINGS.   I don't want to hear that again!
她就是这么教我们的！
They were her words!
但她现在死了！
And now she's dead!
无论你怎么抓狂 你都不能回去
Wring your hands and tear your hair,
but you're not going back there.
你不能回去找他
You're not going back to him.
Angharad!
走吧
Come on!
那个绿洲...
where is this...
到底在什么地方？
this Green Place?
航向向东 走一夜的路程
It's a long night's run, heading east.
我们需要清点一下
We need inventory.
我要你检查所有的枪支弹药
I want you to match every
gun with it's bullets.
我要下去做一些修补
I'm gonna go down and do some repairs.
我们需要有人在后面望风
We need someone down the back.
我去
I'll go.
不行
No.
我要你和大家待在这里
I want you to stay together.
我能做到的
I can do it.
你在这干什么？
What are you doing here?
我看到了
He saw it.
我全都看到了
He saw it all.
我的血包开车碾死了老乔的母种
My own blood bag driving
the rig that killed her.
别这样了
Stop doing that.
停下来
Stop.
大门三次为我敞开 我却失去了所有机会
Three times the gates were open to me.
什么大门
What gates?
英灵殿的大门在等着我
I was awaited in Valhalla.
它在呼唤我的名字
They were calling my name.
我可以跟英灵们同行 与先烈们共餐
I should be walking with the Immortan.
Feasting with the heroes of all time.
我想这不是你的命运
I'd say it was your
manifest destiny not to.
我觉得我是在为更大的荣誉做准备
I thought I was being spared for something great.
我开着追捕车的时候...
I got to... drive a pursuit vehicle.
甚至有一段时间Larry和Barry都停止了侵蚀
For a while even Larry and Barry
stop chewing on my windpipe.
Larry和Barry是谁？
Who're Larry and Barry?
我的肿瘤
My mates.
Larry和Barry
Larry and Barry.
但就算他们没有侵蚀我，我也会高烧折磨
If they don't get me, the Night Fevers will.
这把步枪只剩4发子弹了 所以我觉得已经没什么用了
We only got four for big boy here,
so he's all but useless.
不过...
But...
我们的这把小手枪还可以射29次
we can squirt off this little pinky
about 29 times.
Angharad曾经叫它反叛之种
Angharad used to call it Anti-seed.
埋下一颗就一定会死
Plant one and watch the thing die.
我们耗费了3000加仑的汽油...
We are down 30000 units of gasoline...
19罐硝基...
19 canisters of nitro...
12辆摩托车...
12 assault bikes...
7辆追捕车
7 pursuit vehicles.
全都白搭了
My deficit mounts.
然而现在...
And now, sir...
你又让我们陷入了困境！
you, have us stuck in a quagmire!
老乔！
Hey Joe!
老大
Boss!
你的妻子快不行了！
Your girl is breathing her last!
那孩子呢？
What about the child?
你们还走不走？！
Are you coming Brother?!
等下！
Wait!
孩子也没声了
It's gone awful quiet in there.
剖出来！
Take it out!
把它取出来！
Get it Out!!!
快点！我不想等了！
Come on! I've been called to the torture!
耐心点！
Patience!
噢你在这慢慢悲伤吧！
Oh you stay here with your grief daddy!
我要去找她了
I'll fetch 'em for ya.
小心点！别伤了老乔的宝贝！
Be careful! Protect the assets!!
只需要一颗子弹...
Just one angry shot!...
就能要了她的命！
for Furiosa.
冲啊！
Hut!
真可惜啊
Crying shame.
要是再等一个月...
Another month...
可能就是个健康的孩子！
could've been a viable human!
是男孩吗？
Was it a male?
是个一流的继承人
A-One Alpha Prime.
嘿 Rictus！
Hey Rictus!
你失去了一个弟弟！
You lost a baby brother!
相当的完美
Perfect in every way.
我有过一个弟弟了！
I had a baby brother!!
我有过一个小弟弟！
I had a little baby brother!!!
他很完美！
And he was perfect!!
相当相当的完美！！
Perfect in every way!!!
来吧
Come on.
老大 你别打到那些娘们了
You wouldn't wanna shoot the wives sir.
我只是看看她们的反应
Just prove it
他想要帮忙！
He wants to help!
谁？
Who?!
那个战争之子！
The War Boy!!
他从哪来的？！
Where did he come from?!
我们不是把他推下车了吗！
I thought we threw him off the rig!!
我把车开到前面的高地去！
There is high ground, just beyond that thing!
他是说那棵树
He means the tree.
是的！那棵树！
Yeah. Tree!
把他交给我吧！
Leave him to me!
你们有人看到光亮吗？ 那是在交火吗？
Say, anyone notice that bright light?
Approaching gunfire?
滚下来
Get out.
我可以帮忙 我了解这辆车
I can do this. I know this machine.
没错 他是个老司机
He does. He's a Revhead.
你只剩两发子弹了！
You got two left!
看住他
On him.
屏住气
Don't breathe.
嘿！嘿！嘿！！
Hey! Hey!! Hey!!!
战争男孩！
War Boy!!
我去用绞盘缠住树！
I'll use the winch! Around the tree thing.
拿着这个
Take this.
我们去引擎那
Let's get the engine plates.
你去开车！
You drive the rig!
拿火炬！
Hold the flare!
我已经拿着了！
I am holding the flare!!
再近一点！
Closer!
已经在您眼前了！
It's right in front of your eyes!!
冲！冲啊！
Hut! HUTTT!!!!
血包！
Blood Bag!
我是正义的使者！
I am the scales of justice!
掌控生死的指挥家！
Conductor of the choir of death!
开火！！
Sing for the flock!!
开枪！开他妈的枪！
Sing Brother! Sing!! SINGGGG!!!!
难道他们不知道在朝我们开枪吗？！
Don't they know they're shooting at us?!
换弹！
Guns reload!!!
我从没想过我能做这种不平凡的事情！
I never thought I would do
something as shiny as that!
引擎怎么了？
How're the engines?
又热又渴
Very hot and real thirsty.
嘿 你再继续往前开半公里
Hey. You need to take the rig
half a click down the track.
如果引擎冷却你还没回来怎么办？
What if you're not back
by the time the engines are cooled?
那你们就继续前进
Well you keep moving!
你觉得他会怎么做？
What do you suppose he's gonna do?
以牙还牙
Retaliate first.
我们出发！
Let's go!
你受伤了吗？
Are you hurt?
你在流血
You're bleeding.
那不是他的血
That's not his blood.
这是什么
What is this?
那是人奶
It's Mother's Milk.
没事的
It's okay.
睡吧
Sleep.
好好休息一下
Get some rest.
你这么知道那有绿洲？
How do you know this place even exists?
我出生在那里
I was born there.
那为什么离开了？
Why'd you leave?
我没有离开
I didn't.
我是被掳走的
I was taken as a child.
被偷走的
Stolen.
这种事你之前做过吗？
You've done this before?
很多次了
Many times.
我能够驾驶这辆车...
Now that I drive a War Rig...
是我前所未有的好机会
this is the best shot I'll ever have.
她们呢？
And them?
她们在寻求希望
They are looking for hope.
那你呢？
What about you?
救赎
Redemption.
嘿 那是什么？
Hey. What's that?
我以前见过那个东西
I remember something like that.
救我！
Help me!
救救我！
HELP ME!!!!
求你了 救救我！
Please, help me!
求你了！
Please!
那是个诱饵
That's bait.
待在车里
Stay in the Rig.
快！求你了 快点！ 他们要回来了！
Hurry! Please, hurry up! They will be back!
我是Vuvalini中的一员
I'm one of the Vuvalini!
有众多的母亲
From the Many Mothers!
我的启蒙母亲叫作 Katie Concannon
My initiate mother was Katie Concannon!
我是Mary Jo Bassa的女儿
I am the daughter of Mary Jo Bassa.
我的家族是襁褓之犬
My clan was Swaddle Dog!
是我
It's me.
看你的那双眼眸
There's something in the eyes.
也许是Jo Bassa'的女儿
Perhaps she is Jo Bassa's child.
这是我们的Furiosa
This is our Furiosa.
已经过去多久了？
How long has it been?
7000个日夜了
Seven thousand days.
还有一些已经忘却的日子
Plus the ones I don't remember.
Furiosa.
你的妈妈怎么了？
What happened to your mother?
她去世了
She died.
在我出生的第三天
On the 3rd day.
你从哪里来的？
From where did you come?
西方 山后的要塞
The West. Citadel. Beyond the mountains.
那两个男的 他们是谁？
The men. Who are they?
他们是可以信赖的人
They're reliable.
多亏了他们我们才能到这里
They helped us get here.
你们哪找的这种衣服？
Where did you find such creatures?
真柔软
So soft.
真是一口好牙！
This one has all her teeth!
我等不急想让他们瞧瞧了
I can't wait for them to see it.
瞧？
See?
瞧什么？
See what?
家啊
Home.
那片绿洲
The Green Place.
如果你们是从西方来的...
But if you came from the West...
那你们已经路过了
you passed it.
那片...
The crows.
那片乌鸦横飞的恐怖之地
The creepy place with all the crows.
土地被污染后 我们不得不搬出去
The soil. I We had to get out.
我们没有水
We had no water.
水也是被污染的
And water was filth.
都是酸臭的
It was sour.
然后乌鸦就来了
Then the crows came.
我们什么也种不了
We couldn't grow anything.
那其他人呢？
Where are the others?
什么人？
What others?
其他的母亲呢？
The Many Mothers.
我们是唯一剩下来的
We're the only ones left.
看
Look.
那就是你们所谓的人造卫星
That's what you'd call a satellite.
Miss Giddy曾经跟我们说过
Miss Giddy told us about those.
它最初是给整个地球发收信号的
They used to bounce messages
across the Earth.
电视节目 曾经人人都爱看的电视节目
Shows. Everyone in the old world
had a show.
你觉得在那里还会有人吗？
Do you think there's still
somebody out there?
在那发送信号？
Sending shows?
谁知道呢
Who knows?
都是一片死寂
Those are the Plains of Silence.
好好呆在里面吧小乔 我好像已经失去了新奇感
Stay right where you are little Joey.
Kinda lost it's novelty out here.
你怀孕了？
You having a baby?
是啊
Warlord Junior.
肯定是个丑陋的小暴君
Gonna be so ugly.
说不定是个女孩呢
It could be a girl.
你用那个杀过很多人吧
You killed people with that do ya?
我杀死了我在这里遇到的所有人
Killed everyone I met out here.
爆头的 穿颈的 应有尽有
Headshots. All. Snap! Right in the medulla.
我以为你还会女人一点
I thought you girls were above all that.
过来
Come here.
挑个看看
Take a peek in.
种子！
Seeds!
这是从家乡带来的家产
These are from home.
真正的 有机种子！
Heirlooms. The real thing!
我一直在试着播种
I plant one every chance I get.
在哪？
Where?
到现在 没有存活的 土地都酸化了
So far nothings took. Earth's too sour.
这有很多种类
Ohh so many different kinds.
树木 花卉 水果
Trees, flowers, fruit.
在过去 人人都有这些东西
Back then everyone had their fill!
在过去 我们不需要杀死任何人
Back then, there was no need to snap anybody!
我能和你谈谈吗？
Can I talk to you?
我已经和其他人谈过了
I've talked with the others.
现在是跨越沙漠的最好机会
We're never going to have a better chance
to make it across the salt.
如果我们把卡车留在这 骑上摩托满载出发...
If we leave the rig here, and load the
motorcycles up with as much as we can...
我们至少能够开个160天
we can be able to ride for 160 days.
我们给你留了一辆
One of those bikes is yours.
加满了油
Fully loaded.
非常欢迎你加入我们
You're more than welcome to come with us.
不..不 我会自己走的
N..No, I make my own way.
你知道吗 抱着希望本身就是个错误
You know, hope is a mistake.
如果你没法改变现状...
If you can't fix what's broken, you'll...
你就只能被现实打败
You'll go insane.
你在哪 Max？
Where are you, Max?
你在哪？
Where are you?
救救我们  你答应过会救我们的
Help us. You promised to help us.
爸爸快过来！我们走！
Come on Pa! Let's go!
听好了
Alright.
这里 才是你的家
THIS, is your way home.
我们要回去？
We go back?
回去？  没错
Back?   Yeah.
我以为你已经恢复正常了
I thought you weren't insane anymore.
他怎么说的？
What are they saying?
他想回到我们离开的地方
He wants to go back from where they came.
要塞
The Citadel.
要塞里面有什么？
What's there to find at the Citadel??
绿洲
Green.
还有水！
And water!
那里有取之不尽的水和粮食
There is a ridiculous amounts of
clear water. And a lot of crops.
那里什么都有 只要你不恐高
It's got everything you need.
As long as you're not afraid of heights.
那些水是从哪来的？
Where does the water come from?
老乔从深层的地下打出来的
He pumps it out from deep under the earth.
他控制了他所谓的“纯净之水”
Calls it ‘Aqua Cola',
and claims it all for himself.
并因此来统治一切
And because he owns it,
he owns all of us.
我已经开始讨厌他了
I don't like him already.
穿过山脉得花我们两周的时间
It'll take two weeks just to
scale a wall of mountains.
不需要
No.
我建议直接原路返回
I suggest we go back the same way we came.
穿过峡谷
Through the canyon.
那里应该已经被打通了不是么？ 他的那些人就是从那边通过的
It's open. We know that. Right?
He brought all his war parties through!
所以我们得用武装卡车穿过他们之中
So, we take the War Rig and we charge
it right through the middle of 'em.
可以在路上倒上汽油...
We can decouple the tank at the pass...
断了他们的后路
shut it off behind us.
Ka-Boom!!
那到底我们要怎样拿下要塞呢？
And how exactly do we take the Citadel?
假设那时我们还活着
Assuming we're still alive by then?
如果我们能够阻断道路，那就会变得很容易
If we can block the pass, it'll be easy.
剩下的就只是些老弱病残的了
All that's left are his War Pups,
and War Boys too sick to fight.
我们可以跟着Nux
And we'll be with Nux.
他是个战争之子
He's a War Boy.
押我们回去也是合情合理
He'll be bringing us home.
他的职责就是带回被偷走的东西
Bringing back what's
stolen, as he's meant to.
没错
Yeah.
听起来挺有希望的
Feels like hope.
我喜欢这个计划 我们可以重新开始！
I like this plan. We can start again!
就像过去的那些日子！
Just like the old days!
听着
Look.
这将会是艰难的一天
It will be a hard day.
但我敢保证 你再往前走个160天...
But I guarantee you 160 days riding that way...
见到的还是沙子
there's nothing but.
如果我们原路杀回去 至少我们可以...
At least that way, y'know
we might be able to...
一起...
together...
得到某种所谓的救赎
come across some kind of redemption.
武装车！
War Rig!
那是她的武装卡车！
It's the War Rig!
是他们没错
That's them.
为什么他们回来了？
Why're they going back?
他们是想投降吗？
Do they wish to surrender?
他们开向了峡谷
They're heading for the canyon.
他们是要回去！ 回大本营！
They're going back, to the Citadel!!!
他们知道那里是毫无防备的！
They know it's undefended!!
混蛋！
Bollocks!
你在做什么？         祈祷
What are you doing?    Praying.
向谁祈祷？
To whom?
随便哪个神仙
Anyone that's listening.
做好准备姐妹们！
Here we go girls!
那是我的车！
That's mine!!
他们想抢在我们前面！ 破坏我们的轮胎
They'll try to get in front of us!
Spike our wheels!!
别毁了我的引擎！
Don't blow my engines!
我只是给它加点劲
Gonna nudge 'em. Just a little.
你个败类！你背叛了老乔！
You filth!! You traitored him!
回去
Go.
得缓一缓了！一号引擎熄火了！
Gotta back off! Engine one is gone!
二号也快不行了！
Two's about to blow!
没事的
Great!
你不是老司机吗？
Are you a Black Thumb?
好的，马上去修复一号引擎！
Alright, engine one. Now!
你和我 还有其他人
You and me. 5th wheel.
我们去把水箱解开
We'll unhook the tank.
一枪 一个
One man, one bullet.
我看不见了     Maadi
I can't see.   Maadi.
我看不见了
I can't see.
嘿！
Hey!
他们有飞钩和爬犁！
They've got spears and plows!
把我们的后面勾住了！
They're holding us back!
留三个螺钉 三个
Leave three bolts. Three.
嘿 去你的！
Hey, you!
你还好吗？！
Are you okay?!
我想她受了重伤！
I think she's hurt!
嘿！
Hey!
不！！
NO!!!
嘿！留在我身边！
Hey! Stay with me!
留在我身边！
Stay with me!
Stay with me.
嘿！你还活着吗？
Hey! Are you there?
VALHALLA!!!!!
一号引擎正常了
Engine one's good.
就目前来说
For now.
她受伤了！
She's hurt!!!
受了非常严重的伤！
She's hurt real bad!!
你听到没？
Do you hear that?
待会两个引擎都不行了！
We're gonna see two airborne V8s!
我需要你来开车
I'm gonna need you to drive.
我会把他干掉
I'll get him out of our way.
Rictus!
带我过去！
Take me!
Cheedo！你在干什么？
Cheedo! What are you doing?
好姑娘
Good girl.
过来吧！     不！！
Come here!    NO!!!!
大块头
Big Boy.
这里！手给我！
Here! Here!!
还记得我吗？！
Remember me?!!
他死了！
He's dead!
你先过去 我等锁死油门就跟上你
When you're across safe, I'll
jam the throttle and follow you!
快点过来！
Come on!
快！我们马上快到峡谷了！
Hurry! We're nearly at the pass.
见 证 我！！
W I t n e s s M e!!
Rictus!
为什么她在发出怪声？
Why's she making that noise?
她是在把空气吸入胸腔
She's pumping air into her chest cavity.
随着每一次的呼吸...
She's collapsing her lungs...
她的肺部都在慢慢压缩
one breath at a time.
我知道了
I know.
真的非常抱歉！
I'm so sorry!
我懂  我懂
I know. I know!
坚持住
Hold.
好的
Okay.
放在伤口那 用力按紧
Put there. Press firmly.
嘿！
Hey!
Hey!!
回家了
Home!
到家了！
不 不！ 不 不！不！！
No. No! No, no! No!!
她失血过多
She's exsanguinated.
战斗耗尽了她全部的血液！
Drained all her blood!!
拿着这个
Hold this.
针
Needle.
坚持住！
Come on!
拿着这个！
Take this!
让她保持清醒
Keep her awake.
Furiosa!!
好的！
Okay!
很好
That's it.
举起来
Well, Hold it up!
好的
Okay.
对不起
Sorry.
好的 很好
There you go. Okay!
Max.
我叫Max！
My name is Max!
这是我的名字
That's my name.
停下！
Brake!
出来现身！
Reveal yourself!
他带了什么东西
He's got something.
是不死老乔！
It's Immortan Joe!
不死老乔死了！！
IMMORTAN JOE IS DEAD!!!
Furiosa!
她回来了！
She's back!
让他们上去！
Let them up!!
Let them up!!!
让他们上去！！
Let them up!!!!
让他们上去！
LET THEM UP!!!!!
我们是该去什么地方...
'Where must we go...
还是要在这片荒芜之地寻求更好的自己？
we who wander this wasteland
in search of our better selves?'
史上第一人
The First History Man.
谢谢观看更多优质字幕请访问www.haosub.com